export const set6 = [
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">6</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["47", "27", "37", "57"],
    answer: "37"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">4</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">1</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["24", "34", "44", "54"],
    answer: "34"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">6</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">1</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">4</span> + <span class="number-term">6</span> + <span class="number-term">8</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["38", "28", "48", "58"],
    answer: "38"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">4</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">6</span> + <span class="number-term">1</span> + <span class="number-term">8</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">4</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["29", "49", "59", "39"],
    answer: "39"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">8</span> + <span class="number-term">1</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">1</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["29", "49", "59", "39"],
    answer: "39"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">6</span> + <span class="number-term">4</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">4</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">1</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">9</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["39", "49", "29", "59"],
    answer: "39"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">6</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">4</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["55", "45", "35", "25"],
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">1</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">4</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">8</span> + <span class="number-term">9</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["32", "42", "52", "62"],
    answer: "42"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">8</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["35", "25", "45", "55"],
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">8</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["28", "48", "38", "58"],
    answer: "38"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">7</span> + <span class="number-term">3</span> + <span class="number-term">8</span> + <span class="number-term">5</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> + <span class="number-term">9</span> + <span class="number-term">1</span> + <span class="number-term">2</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["29", "39", "49", "59"],
    answer: "39"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">715</span> + <span class="number-term">716</span> + <span class="number-term">717</span> + <span class="number-term">718</span> + <span class="number-term">719</span> + <span class="number-term">720</span> + <span class="number-term">721</span> + <span class="number-term">722</span> + <span class="number-term">723</span> + <span class="number-term">724</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["7175", "7195", "7215", "7235"],
    answer: "7195"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">922</span> + <span class="number-term">923</span> + <span class="number-term">924</span> + <span class="number-term">925</span> + <span class="number-term">926</span> + <span class="number-term">927</span> + <span class="number-term">928</span> + <span class="number-term">929</span> + <span class="number-term">930</span> + <span class="number-term">931</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["9265", "9245", "9285", "9305"],
    answer: "9265"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">543</span> + <span class="number-term">544</span> + <span class="number-term">545</span> + <span class="number-term">546</span> + <span class="number-term">547</span> + <span class="number-term">548</span> + <span class="number-term">549</span> + <span class="number-term">550</span> + <span class="number-term">551</span> + <span class="number-term">552</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["5465", "5485", "5505", "5475"],
    answer: "5475"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">274</span> + <span class="number-term">275</span> + <span class="number-term">276</span> + <span class="number-term">277</span> + <span class="number-term">278</span> + <span class="number-term">279</span> + <span class="number-term">280</span> + <span class="number-term">281</span> + <span class="number-term">282</span> + <span class="number-term">283</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["2765", "2785", "2805", "2825"],
    answer: "2785"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">135</span> + <span class="number-term">136</span> + <span class="number-term">137</span> + <span class="number-term">138</span> + <span class="number-term">139</span> + <span class="number-term">140</span> + <span class="number-term">141</span> + <span class="number-term">142</span> + <span class="number-term">143</span> + <span class="number-term">144</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1415", "1375", "1395", "1435"],
    answer: "1395"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">326</span> + <span class="number-term">327</span> + <span class="number-term">328</span> + <span class="number-term">329</span> + <span class="number-term">330</span> + <span class="number-term">331</span> + <span class="number-term">332</span> + <span class="number-term">333</span> + <span class="number-term">334</span> + <span class="number-term">335</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["3275", "3295", "3305", "3315"],
    answer: "3305"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">757</span> + <span class="number-term">758</span> + <span class="number-term">759</span> + <span class="number-term">760</span> + <span class="number-term">761</span> + <span class="number-term">762</span> + <span class="number-term">763</span> + <span class="number-term">764</span> + <span class="number-term">765</span> + <span class="number-term">766</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["7595", "7635", "7575", "7615"],
    answer: "7615"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">918</span> + <span class="number-term">919</span> + <span class="number-term">920</span> + <span class="number-term">921</span> + <span class="number-term">922</span> + <span class="number-term">923</span> + <span class="number-term">924</span> + <span class="number-term">925</span> + <span class="number-term">926</span> + <span class="number-term">927</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["9215", "9235", "9225", "9195"],
    answer: "9225"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">839</span> + <span class="number-term">840</span> + <span class="number-term">841</span> + <span class="number-term">842</span> + <span class="number-term">843</span> + <span class="number-term">844</span> + <span class="number-term">845</span> + <span class="number-term">846</span> + <span class="number-term">847</span> + <span class="number-term">848</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["8445", "8405", "8465", "8435"],
    answer: "8435"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">260</span> + <span class="number-term">261</span> + <span class="number-term">262</span> + <span class="number-term">263</span> + <span class="number-term">264</span> + <span class="number-term">265</span> + <span class="number-term">266</span> + <span class="number-term">267</span> + <span class="number-term">268</span> + <span class="number-term">269</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["2645", "2625", "2665", "2605"],
    answer: "2645"
  },
  {
    question: `
        <div class="horizontal-question">
          <span><span class="number-term">131</span> + <span class="number-term">132</span> + <span class="number-term">133</span> + <span class="number-term">134</span> + <span class="number-term">135</span> + <span class="number-term">136</span> + <span class="number-term">137</span> + <span class="number-term">138</span> + <span class="number-term">139</span> + <span class="number-term">140</span> = </span>
        </div>
      `,
    options: ["1335", "1395", "1355", "1375"],
    answer: "1355"
  }
];